topchatsites.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - TopChatSites

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to the TopChatSites Services as provided by Bridgestone International Group, Inc. We have created this Privacy Policy to tell you what information we collect, how we use that information. This Privacy Policy does not address the privacy practices of any third parties that we do not own, control, or are affiliated with. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

By visiting and/or using our Services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy, and to use the information it contains to help you make informed decisions.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT OR RECEIVE

 **Information we collect about you**

 **In General.** We may collect Personal Information, including Sensitive Data, and other information. “Personal Information” means individually identifiable information that would allow us to determine the actual identity of, and contact, a specific living person. Sensitive Data includes information, comments or content (e.g. video, profile, comments) that you optionally provide that may reveal personal details to the extent you have chosen. By providing Sensitive Data to us, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of Sensitive Data as permitted by applicable privacy laws. We may also collect your geolocation information with your consent. We may collect this information through the mobile application, or related online services. By using the Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse and retain data related to the provision of the Service. 

**Information you provide.** In the course of downloading, installing and using the Services you may be required to provide certain information to enable the functionalities of TopChatSites as an example, your device type or IP address, your operating system and/or browser, cookies or other information. Users are reminded that they control the information they share and are responsible for adjusting settings in the hardware or software they use. 

You agree that prior to using our Services, you were given an opportunity to review our privacy policy and you agreed to these terms. To the extent you maintain your settings, you authorized TopChatSites to collect data and information for the purposes of providing this service.

During the course of your usage of the Service, in order to access features that may be offered now or in the future, you may be required to provide us with Personal Information which may include your name, e-mail address, physical address, and phone number.

You understand and agree that your use of these Service features is at your discretion. It is your decision whether or not to use certain features or functionalities, all such Personal Information is given voluntarily.

Through this service you may stream or otherwise deliver user-generated content, in addition features and functionalities may allow you to create a user profile or post other content. All such features allow you to disclose certain personal information of your choosing. Users agree that the ultimate responsibility for the details, information and/or content they share publicly, with other users is theirs to make. Users are strongly discouraged from sharing financial details, their home address or other sensitive information. Users agree and understand that such information they share is at their discretion, TopChatSites assumes no liability for these personal choices. TopChatSites may chose to take remedial action, at their discretion, when they feel that certain activities violate our terms and conditions, or other laws and regulations.

 **Information from other sources.** We, and the third-party service providers, which we may chose to employ, may use analytics services to evaluate and improve user experience through our service. Such data and information will be aggregated, and only used to provide information about your usage, to the extent necessary to provide you with the services you have indicated an interest in.

 **Opting Out of Certain Functions.** By adjusting your browser, hardware, or mobile device settings according to the requirements of the manufacturer or carrier, you can disable certain features in your privacy settings. You understand that it is your obligation to make these adjustments to make this decision. You are also advised that if you opt out of any such service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Service.

 **How we use the information we collect**

 **In General.** We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver and improve our services, and manage our business;
  * provide customer support;
  * analyze your use of the incorporated Services to develop features and deliver content of interest to you.
  * to gather analytics information to improve the functionality of the Service.
  * to verify your eligibility to use certain features of the service, to contact you in reply to your complaints, or to exercise any rights in our Terms of Use.
  * or to perform functions or services as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

 **With whom we share your information**

In addition for sharing listed above to allow functionalities of the Service, you as a user of TopChatSites shall have consented to have your content to appear as viewable by other users of the Service to the degree your settings have authorized.

 **Personal information.** We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

 **Service providers.** From time to time, we may employ third party service providers to carry out certain features or functionalities of this service (including, but not limited to, moderation, technical support, or payment processing) these third parties will be required to handle all data and information according to these policies.

 **Other Situations.** We may disclose your information, including personal information:

In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our terms and policies.

 **Aggregated and/or non-personal information.** We may use and share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with affiliates and third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Service and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see.

 **Children's privacy**

Although our Service is a general audience Service, we require that our Users are of the legal age required to enter into a contract. This Service is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us [privacy@topchatsites.com.](mailto:privacy@topchatsites.com "Contact Us")

 **Onward transfer and consent to international processing**

We are a growing corporation with users and operations in multiple countries, including the European Union. We have developed data practices designed to assure information is appropriately protected but we ask our Users to be aware of the privacy and data protection laws in the jurisdiction in which they reside. You acknowledge that, the ultimate responsibility for the information you choose to share is yours.

 **No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

 **Application Stores and External Websites or Services**

Your app store (e.g., iTunes or Google Play) may collect certain information in connection with your use of the Service, such as Personal Information, Payment Information, Geolocational Information, and other usage-based data. We have no control over the collection of such information by a third-party app store, and any such collection or use will be subject to that third party’s applicable privacy policies.

The Service may contain links to third-party websites. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of these websites. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third-party websites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on the Service. By accessing the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, our use of the Information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect the Information. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

 **To Contact Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@topchatsites.com.](mailto:privacy@topchatsites.com "Contact Us") with “Privacy Policy” in the subject line. For all other questions, please use the information provided in the Terms of Service to contact us.
